One dream, one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Mark maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
That lion dog's a giant!
Is it a pet?
This is a waste of time.
Shouldn't we ask around?
It wouldn't matter even if we did.
They won't answer us.
The people here are all under
the Shogun Orochi's influence.
You sure?
There's lots of normal-looking people
here who don't seem like bad guys.
Some towns people have
been here a very long time
until 20 years ago this
was a vibrant castle town.
And many of the businesses
have stayed since then,
but as for the houses, Orochi's
subordinates seized all the ones they liked;
only the merchants who they
deemed essential could stay;
the others were thrown from their
homes—they can never return.
This is such a cruel place!
Make no mistake!
mistake
A sumo wrestler? But why?
Hmm, must be something crazy
going on in the town square.
Well, since a sumo
wrestler came flying out,
I'm gonna guess it's a sumo match.
Once again!
The Yokozuna, the flower capital,
stands victorious! Here he is!
Who remains to challenge Ulashima?
Does anyone dare?
Still nothing but weaklings, eh?
Another one.
It looks like Unashima is
still hungry for new opponents,
he has defeated 19 men already!
As for the number of bones that have been
broken, let's check in with the doctor!
That's 10 arm bones, 15 leg bones,
looking like 52 ribs, four
skulls, and let's see.
Seven backbones—I think that's 88 bones
in total and four wrestlers who flew away.
He shows no mercy;
his strength surpasses man.
What you see before
you is an undefeatable!
undefeatable
Now, let's hear a round
of applause for Unashima!
A quick note, this is a
special match to the open.
Anyone who gets best
Unashima wins 500 gold coins!
Go back down now, you guys!
Yeah, I'll bet on you!
That prize is gonna be ours!
We know just what to do!
Put those scandals in their place!
Nice!
Crack their skulls!
Looks like a fight!
Get ready!
And go!
Okiku, you accepted my
invitation after all.
I'm glad you finally came
around and decided to marry me.
How awkward.
You are way too big to hide behind me.
Well, this is certainly a surprise!
There's a woman here who is
apparently engaged to Unashima!
Ah!
Loved by a Yokozuna, I'm a little
jealous, and she came here to support him!
This is a big day for our champion!
Do you have a special someone?
It's not fair!
I want to be his wife!
For real? Never.
He just got that idea in his big head.
The man can be quite forward, as you saw.
Oh, Kiku, I'll have a wrestling
match in Bekori Town today, Pei.
I hope you'll come so I can
show you just how strong I am.
I assure you, I will
not budge on the issue.
Fair enough, then.
Hey, you guys!
We're looking for someone! Can you help?
A little girl!
Her name is Tama!
Can you tell me where the
boss of this town is at?
She should be there!
I'm so angry!
It's not fair!
I'm good at her suspender!
She looks kind of big, but I guess
that's just right for Urashima.
No!
I'm the only one for him!
They're all ignoring you.
Hurry and do me a favor, would you?
Grab Okiku, bring her over here.
Congrats boss, it seems
you're quite the charmer.
Next you're gonna have to
train us in the arts of love.
Okiku.
Fine, we might tell ourselves.
Let's go.
Hey lady, Urashima told
us to get you, come on.
We've got stuff to do, move.
Knock him out!
It's your deal, huh?
What?
That was a pretty good charge.
But a nice slap is still my favorite.
Lady, why are you resisting? Stop.
Please let me go.
You're going to cut an unarmed man?
I don't even have any clothes on.
Hey, Kaku!
Uh, Throw, why didn't you stop that guy?
Sorry.
But I couldn't cut down
a man in his underwear.
Just didn't feel right.
One, two! One, two!
Besides, I have a feeling she's
not half as helpless as she looks.
She's too low class to even be here.
How did she get through the
gate in the first place?
Kick her out!
She's got some nerve.
I knew she was a trip
the second I saw her.
What would you peasants know?
I'm a member of the
warrior class, damn it.
You commoners are nothing but
filth beneath my feet, Perk.
Your lives are meaningless
to someone like me.
I may spare you, or I may slay you.
There's nothing you can do.
So,
Okiku, having heard that,
ignore those vermin,
and be mine! Please!
I won't take no for an answer!
What I see are people just
trying to survive, not vermin.
Ye vulgar beast, the only filth
before me is thine own heart.
She cut off this top knot.
Whoa, sweet!
Nice one!
Go Kaku!
This is getting fun!
The Commodore woman rejected him hard!
His top knot has been violated!
The boss should be coming
for us any time now?
Oh, Kiku!
You betrayed me!
And brought me shame!
Ah!
Why did I do that in public?
What was I thinking?
He's become a demon of fury!
Okiku!
Oh no!
I know that pose!
That's the far-bang slap!
It sends you straight to hell!
Can't we talk this through?
Let's not be hasty.
A shame.
In the end, you are the kind of
beast who would strike a woman.
And I shall strike you dead!
Now come, come!
You won't slip!
You rat!
How in blazes did you counter my attack?
And for that matter,
how do you know Okikupe?
Get away!
I have to tear Okiku
apart with my bare hands.
Or my reputation will be ruined.
Alright, I get it.
Let me stretch.
Let's
see
you
get through me!
Huh?
Scared?
I've never lost a sumo match!
I said move!
I'll crush you!
But he said for slap!
He's dodging every one of those attacks!
This is really fast!
Keep it up, brat!
But you can't win if you don't fight back!
Ear splitter!
Eye splitter!
Hold on!
Pretty sure that's not legal, you cheater!
I don't care!
I am...
A Yokozuna!
Fine.
No rules.
Hold him, sir!
we have a problem.
Huh?
The Yokozuna got his topknot
chopped off by some lady?
He might start a riot.
He tried to take revenge, and
now he's fighting some guy.
Uh, who cares?
And what do you want me to do about it?
I don't have time for sumo.
I'm too busy tearing this
little girl's cheek off.
Have mercy on me!
You can have your booboon back!
Just don't pinch me!
Oh, you're getting pinched, kid.
Sorry about it.
You shouldn't have gone around
mentioning the Kozuki clan.
The Kozuki clan is gonna come
back, and then you'll die!
Even a dumb brat like you knows that uttering
the name Kozuki is a serious offense.
You won't get off easy.
You should have agreed to work
with us while you had the chance.
It's been long enough.
Stop chasing after ghosts.
There hasn't been a
Kozuki here in 20 years.
We shut them down after they
tried to destroy the land of Wano.
They're nothing but evil spirits now
Scram, you pest!
And Okiku, you dug your own
grave, you little ingrate, eh?
You have no right to turn down a request
from a member of the warrior class,
you peasant.
You shamed me.
My honor demands that
I smash your head in.
Then it's no problem, right?
Go ahead and smash me
if you think you can.
That should be easy for
a champ like you, right?
You mock me?
Listen!
You know who I am!
I'm the greatest Yokozuna in all Wano!
All banks slip!
What the heck is that?
A rope, maybe?
True, you may be a Yokozuna, but me?
I'm the man who's going to
be the king of the pirates!
I'm so scared!
Please help me love me!
Now come, come!
Huh?
GIANT!
You won't fly!
Toss Conney!
Don't mention me!
Whoa!
Saul, am I safe now, or what?
The Yokozuna is out!
I don't even know where he is!
He really lost!
After all those fights he
lost to that odd little guy?
Now I'm a Yokozuna too!
If anybody else wants to
fight, then bring it on!
I think that'll do it.
The boss is bound to show up.
Ain't better!
I know that guy!
Wait!
I know him too!
He killed the magistrate, didn't he?
You wanna fight about it?
Don't tell me he's allies with that sumo!
Hey!
We want to fight the boss of this town!
Tell them we're here to save Tama!